Jacobs, Arthur Additional Arbitration Papers 6139
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New Paltz CSD Yorktown CSD; Correspondence, 1977-1994. (Box 2)
  - Rutgers University/ Administrative, Professional and Supervisory Personnel, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Rutgers University/ Susan Bonner, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Ryder Truck Rental/ International Assn. of Machinists and Aerospace, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Rye City school District/ Rye Teachers Assoc., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - City of Rye/ Rye Police Association, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - St. Anthony Hospital/ Hospital Employees Labor Program of Metropolitan Chicago, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - St. John's Episcopal Hospital/ St. Johns Federation of Health Professionals, NYSUT, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Sands Hotel & Casino/ Hotel and Restaurant Employees Int'l Union local 54, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Sanyo Automotive Parts/ IBT Local 819, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Saybolt/ Local 8-337, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Village of Scardale/ CSEA local 860, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Scarsdale Public Library/ CSEA, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Schott Brothers Inc./ ACTWU local 169, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Schultze & Burch Biscuit Co./ Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers Int'l Union, Local #1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Sealtest/ District 15, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Sheller-Globe Corp/ ACTWU, local 1374, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Shredded Metals Recycling/ United Steelworkers of America Local 6572, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Smith loyal/ Unite, Neckwear and Accessories Division NY Joint Board, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Social Security Admin/ AFGE 2369, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Social Security Admin, Bureau of Dist. Office Operations NY Region/ NY-NJ Council of Dist. Office Locals of AFGE, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Somers CSD/ Somers Faculty Assoc. NYSUT, AFI, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Somers CSD/ Somers School Related Personnel, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - South Bend Community School Corp./ AFSCME C1. 62, Local 686, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - South Orangetown Cental District Bo #1/ Education Assoc. of S. Orangetown NYSUT, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - South Orangetown CSD/ S. Orangetown Teachers Assn., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Southern Indiana gas Electric Co./ I/B/ of Electrical Workers local 702, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Southern Ohio Coal Co/ United Mine Workers of America District 31, Local 1949, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Spring Valley, Village of/ Spring Valley PBA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Staten Island Development/ AFSCME, Council 82 Center, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Drs Harddand Jerome Stein/ International Union of Industrial, Service Transport and Health Employees District #6, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Suffolk Co. Water Authority/ Utility Workers of America local 393, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Sugar Loaf UFSD/ Sugar Loaf Teachers Assoc., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Tarrytowns BoE/ Teachers Assoc. of the Tarrytowns, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Tarrytown, Village pf/ CSEA local 860, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Toasted Pies Inc./ IBT Local 802, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Tompkins Industries/ Sheet Metal Workers local 20, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Trilborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority/ Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Assn., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Trissi Inc./ ACTWU-Shirt, Leisurewear, robe, glove and rainwear workers Union, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Troy, City of/ CSEA Local 842, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Trylon Robe Co./ ACWA - Shirt andleisurewear Division, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Tuckahoe UFSD/ Tuckahoe Teachers Assn., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Tuxedo UFSD/ Brian Cullen, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Tuxedo UFSD #3/ Tuxedo Teachers Assoc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Union News Co./ Culinary Workers of NY Local 923, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - United Parcel Service/ IBT Local 676, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development/ American Federation of govt. Employees Local 911, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Valley CSD #1 BoE/ Valley Central Teachers Assoc., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Valley Stream BoE, District 13/ Valley Stream Teachers Assn., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Valley Stream UFSD #24/ Valley Stream Teachers Assn. Local 1633, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Variety Knit Corp./ Shirt and Leisurewear Division, NY Joint Board ACTWU, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Venture Stores Inc./ IBT, Local 743, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Walden, Village of/ PBA, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Walgreen Eastern Company/ Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union Local 100, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Wappingers CSD/ Wappingers Congress of Teachers, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Warwick, town of/ CSEA, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Warwick Valley CSD/ Warwick Valley Teacher Assn., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Washingtonville CSD/ CSEA, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Washingtonville B.O.E./ Washingtonville Teachers Assoc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Town of Webb/ Webb PBA, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Webutuck CSD/ Webutuck Teachers Assn., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - West Islip BoE/ West Islip Teachers Assn., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - West Mill Clothes and Tuxedo Trousers/ NY Joint Board ACTWU, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Westbury UFSD BoE/ Westbury Teachers Assn, NYSUT, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Westchester Co/ Westchester C3 Federation of Teachers #2431 NYSUT, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Westchester Comm. College/ Westchester C3 Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - White Plains, City of/ CSEA local 860, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Windsor, town of/ Town of Windsor PBA, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Wire Sales Co/ United Steelworkers of America Local 6102, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Woodridge, Village of/ CSEA, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Xenia Pleating/ ACTWU local 169, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Yonkers BoE/ Yonkers School Administrators, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - City of Yonkers/ CSEA, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Yonkers, City of/ Local 628 International Assoc. of Firefighters, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - City of Yonkers/ Uniformed Fire Officers Assn., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Yonkers, City of/ Anthony Suozzi, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Yorkstown CSD BoE/ Yorktown Congress of Teachers Local 1724 NYSUT AFT, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Unidentified School District/ Unidentified Teacher (Miller 1986) (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Arbitrations 1958-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence 1977-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Jacobs Arbitration - additional, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 155)